Oh, yeah.
Oh look at her, she's gorgeous.
Oh, yes.
Yeah-huh.
She's big, but fast.
Uh, what are you watching?
The boat network.
There's a boat network?
Yeah, 322,
Right between the allergy channel
And the mexican dessert channel.
Why are you watching a show about boats?
'cause all week long
They're having this big "win a boat" contest.
They're asking a bunch of boat trivia questions,
And whoever texts in the most correct answers, wins the boat.
Ah, so that's why you have
Your big book of boats out.
Nah, I was just pressing some flowers.
Ah, pretty.
What?
Come here.
Check out this video these guys sent to icarly.
Now, before beginning a surgical procedure,
I'd first put on my blindfold.
Blindfold?
But how will you see?
Ooooh, ooooh, ooooh, ooooh!
Who are these guys?
Uh, fleck and dave.
So why'd they send us that video?
Uhhh, let's read the email.
In 1997,
Famous boat designer, Joe catania, built what?
The world's largest dinghy!
Okay, they say...
And freddie.
Ooh, they mentioned you.
No, I added me.
Just read.
Click there.
Carly.
Sam.
If you don't play Our video...
We're gonna eat bananas till we explode!
Play our video!
Sam, play our video!
You think we should play their video?
I don't know,
I kinda wanna see 'em explode.
Okay, as you know--
Here at icarly
--we get tons of videos sent to us from you guys,
Our fans.
Most of 'em suck cheese.
Sam?
Anyway, a few days ago--
We got a video from two dudes named...
Fleck and dave.
And it was so good...
We invited 'em right here To meet you live On the webbernet.
So pull your hands apart...
And take it down for...
We are here.
Uh, plastic spoons?
They were out of forks.
Walk away, gibby.
All right, now this is fleck.
Fleck.
And he'd be dave.
I'd be.
He'd be.
And you guys make All kinds of wacky videos
And put 'em up On splashface, right?
Yeah, we do.
And how long have you guys Been doing this together?
Well, we first met,
Wait when did we meet?
Uh, i think it was back In the 1962 olympics.
Right, in fresno.
Now, the video These guys sent us?
Pretty dang hi-larious.
The opposite of low-larious.
Oh, i begged her Not to say that.
I should've listened.
Playback.
Now, that my blindfold Is secure,
It's time to anna-sthee-ziate The patient.
Anna-sthee-ziate?
Breathe deeply,
There you go,
Breathe in...
It's time for... Surgery.
Now, i take my scalpel
And make a small incision,
Just above The patient's bellybutton.
I'm bleeding.
Is that supposed to happen?
No, stop bleeding!
How?!
You're making a mess!
Help me, help me!
More anna-sthee-ziation.
Hmmmm, hmmmm.
Mm-hmm
So, what do you think?
Rocking smoothie.
Yeah, it's like sweet, but...
Whoooaaa, ahhhhhhh!
Oww, uh-ah-ah!
You're hot, right?
Yeah.
We liked that.
What's in these smoothies?
Jalapeno juice.
The spicy mixes with the sweet
To give 'em A one-of-a-kind evil taste.
No chiz.
Chiz.
Ahh.
So what'd you guys think
Of being on icarly tonight?
Awesome.
Insane.
We've been dying to get One of our videos on your show.
Like forever.
Aah.
You know,
Our video was viewed
By more people tonight on icarly
Than our last video was viewed In a whole year?
You guys got vicious power.
Oh, we know.
So you guys working On anything new?
Yeah, our next video's Gotta be like
Off-the-charts awesome.
How come?
My parents want me to quit Making videos with fleck.
Why?
'cause his dad Doesn't like me.
My dad hates you.
But it's not just that.
He thinks comedy videos Are a waste of time.
So who cares what he thinks?
Some people pay attention To their parents.
Losers.
You guys know about ishorts?
Sure.
I love that site.
Well, they're doing This thing.
Best comedy video submitted By the end of this month,
Wins five grand.
Five grand?
Grand means thousand.
I'm hip.
Hip people don't say hip.
Fine, i'm down, i'm cool,
I'm jiggly,
Whatever.
Wow, that's a hot smoothie.
So what's your Guy's next video gonna be?
Well, that depends.
On?
Us coming up with an idea.
So you got nothing
Nada.
Zero.
Oh, if you guys Want us to help--
Oh yes, we do.
Yeah.
I think they want our help.
My tongue needs help.
These things are good But way too much heat.
Seriously, i'm sweatin'.
Feel my pit.
Feel my no.
Who likes turkey breasts?
Dude, would you get out--
Gimme two.
You texted?
Yeah, i need your help To win the boat.
The contest Is still going on?
All week, i've been watching The boat network
24/7 for the past three days
And so far i've texted in At least 14 right answers.
So you think you'll win?
Maybe,
But i've gotta shower And i'm worried
They're gonna ask Another question While i'm in there.
You haven't showered In three days?
No.
Eww.
I know.
Yesterday, i was just smelling Kinda french,
But now it's getting really bad.
Ohh, will you help me?
I'm not giving you A sponge bath
While you watch tv.
Not after last time.
No, see i've angled These mirrors
So i can take a shower And still see the tv.
So if they ask a question, I can jump right on it.
You know, you're a grown man.
I just need your help Adjusting this last mirror
Once i get in the shower.
Go for it.
Stay right there!
Okay, a little to the left.
Okay.
Little more.
Stop!
I can see the tv perfectly now.
Okay, i'm gonna shower.
Is that a birthmark On your butt?
Don't look at it!
You're overreacting.
You haven't seen overreacting Young man.
What were you thinking?
Get out--
Or i'm gonna call the cops.
Your dad is loud.
You make him loud.
He overreacted.
You can't use Another man's toothbrush!
Come in.
How's it goin' fellas?
So, do you guys Like our purple outfits?
Totally.
All right, let's get The video shoot started.
Okay, i'll get my dad To bring his car in here.
I can just push it in.
But, be careful.
He-be-be-bleh-bleh.
Hey, do you wanna help fleck Push the car in?
Why me?
Feel my muscle.
Yeah, i better do it.
So this is our script?
Yeah, i just put down Some basic ideas
'cause i figured you guys Wanna improvise and stuff.
Yeah, on icarly Sam and i usually--
Ahh, what'd you do?
Fleck?
Yeah, what's up?
How did my dad's car Get purple?
I've used about 12 cans Of this stuff.
Dude, my dad's gonna Murder me.
I brought salad.
You said he was cool with us Using his car in our video.
Yeah, but he didn't say We could paint it purple.
Our characters come From a purple planet.
Who cares what planet--
If we're playing purpepulons From the planet purpleonia,
Then our vehicle's Gotta be purple.
Don't you guys agree with that?
Argh, augh.
Wait, whoa okay I know you're upset
But hedge clippers Are never the answer.
Well.
Never the answer.
Hey, you guys ever watch The mexican dessert channel?
Dude, when my dad Sees this car,
He's gonna explode.
Get that on film And you'll definitely win
The ishorts competition.
Your dad's never gonna know His car was purple.
See this.
I bought paint remover.
How is one ounce Of paint remover
Gonna clean up this whole car?
I got two.
You're mean to me.
You know i'm getting sick And tired of your criticism.
Are you?
He-be-ble-bleh.
Guys, let's chill out A little, okay?
It's totally normal for friends
To get on each other's nerves Once in a while.
Ha-ha, you have no idea What it's like
Working with this nut-job.
What do you mean by that?
You always gotta stress About every little thing.
You cause my stress.
You give me chest pains And i'm only 13.
Oww.
You know, it's your fault.
This is getting Outta control.
We need to fix this.
I got it.
Are you kidding me?
This is all your fault.
No, it's all your fault!
How is it my fault?
You're the one who came up With the idea
In the first place.
I don't like seeing Purple boys fight, all right?
Either you guys are friends,
Or you're not.
Now, what's it gonna be?
Not.
So not.
Not!
I didn't get this.
Really?
How does this game work?
Easy.
You just gotta try to move Your hands out of the way
Before i smack 'em.
Well, then when do you--
Uh!
Oww.
That's not fun.
Then have faster reflexes.
I don't wanna play this--
Awwww!
It's okay,
You're doing awesome.
How can you just stand there And play with freddie?
What?
Fleck and dave.
Oh, they broke up.
Aah!
Ooh, you're getting better At this.
Come on, those guys Were hilarious together.
So?
We need to fix this.
Let's go talk to 'em.
They said they'd never speak To each other ever again.
Well, then you go Talk to fleck
And i'll go talk to dave.
Fine.
But one thing first.
What?
Uh-oh!
I won the boat,
I won the boat, i won the boat,
Won the boat, i won it.
Won the boat.
You won the boat?
No.
Yes, i won the boat!
Ahoy, landlubbers.
Landlubbers?
Yeah, i do lub the land.
Look at the boat i won.
Wow.
Nice.
Barca.
Cool.
Do you guys realize
What we can do with this boat?
Sell it and pay somebody To get that cat out of the wall?
That cat's not still In the wall.
Aah!
Game over.
Um, i don't think This is gonna be enough Paint remover.
This is all fleck brought.
Jerky fleck.
So your dad was pretty mad, Huh?
Well, first he yelled.
Understandable.
Then he did this To my laptop.
With a hammer.
Yeah, that's probably gonna Void the warranty.
Whatever.
I don't need fleck.
I'll just make A funny video by myself
And i'll still win The ishorts contest.
I don't need dave To win that ishorts contest.
That boy was holding me back.
Come on, you guys Are way funny together.
He's only funny When i'm standin' next to him.
Without me, dave's just A grumpy head of lettuce.
Dude, your relationship With dave is really important.
You don't wanna just throw away
Something that's...
You dip your french fries In your smoothie?
Oh, yeah.
Try it.
Huh, okay,
But it seems kinda weird
'cause the french fry's All salty,
And the smoothie's all...
Oh man, you're a genius.
Yep.
But seriously...
Wait, What were we talking about?
Yeah, i know Fleck's really funny,
But that doesn't give him The right to ruin my life.
Maybe you're exaggerating A little?
In the last three months,
He pushed me off my roof.
Well, i'm sure He didn't mean to--
He set my pants on fire.
Wow that's rude, but--
And he sat on my sister.
Yeah, but--
You must be frustrated.
Yeah, you have no idea What it's like
To work with someone Who's an irresponsible maniac.
Ohhhh, i kinda do.
For real.
You can't understand What it's like
Working with someone Who's always putting the squish
On good ideas 'cause they're "dangerous"
Or "flammable".
Nah, i get it.
Sometimes carly can be Like that.
And usually, Sam doesn't even get there
Till like two minutes Before we start the show.
Fleck's always late Like that.
Irritating, right?
Well, yeah.
And, you know, i'm the one Who plans out the show,
And i put everything On these cute little
Pastel colored index cards,
And half the time She doesn't even look at 'em.
Fleck blew his nose In one of my index cards.
Ewww.
Yeah, ewww.
Like one time We were trying to think
Of a funny icarly bit,
So i go, "hey, why don't we "put freddie in a diaper,
"take him to the zoo, "and make him sneak
Into the tiger habitat."
That'd be epic.
I know, but carly goes,
"oh no, what if the tiger Mauls freddie?"
Ooooooooh...
Wait, wait.
She wanted to put freddie In a diaper and make him
Sneak into the tiger habitat?
Yuh-huh.
What if he got mauled?
That's what i said.
Yeah, maybe you are Better off without dave.
That's what i'm saying.
Yeah, maybe you are Better off without fleck.
It's just kinda suckish
When i'm the one Who does all the hard work,
And then someone else takes Half the credit, you know?
Yeah i know. It's called my life.
Ahoy!
Gibby ho!
Hey, spencer.
So what do you think Of my hot new boat?
It's awesome.
Thanks.
The s.s. placeholder?
That's its name?
For now.
Cool.
So where you gonna dock it?
Down at the seattle pier,
Why?
That's pretty expensive.
How do you know?
My cousin keeps a boat Down at the pier.
Costs him like a grand a month.
A grand?
Grand means thousand.
I know what a grand means.
How am i gonna afford A thousand bucks a month?
Sell the boat?
I'm just brainstorming.
I guess i'll just Keep the boat here
In the parking lot,
And then take it to the water When it's time for boating.
So can i come aboard?
If you say it right.
Permission to come aboard,
Captain?
Permission yeah!
Get up here!
Aye aye.
Step, hold on tight,
There you go, all right.
So there you go.
Thanks.
So can i be, like, Your assistant?
You mean, my boat boy?
I love that.
Okay.
But first,
I'll need to christen you With this novelty
Nonalcoholic champagne bottle.
Do it.
Yeah, i'm a boat boy!
Wooooooo!
Sh'boom.
Hey.
So how'd things go With fleck?
Not great.
Dave?
Bad.
Then i don't know How we're gonna fix those guys.
Yeah.
I don't even get How they made videos together
As long as they did.
I know.
It sounds like he was A nightmare to work with.
The worst.
Wait.
Which guy are you Talking about?
Fleck.
Whoa, no-no-no-no-no.
Fleck's the cool one.
Huh?
Dave's all "mister responsible" And like doesn't even get
The whole spontaneous Creative process thing.
Oh, so you think All the stuff dave does to make
The fleck and dave videos happen Means nothing.
Well, not as much as what Happens on camera.
Sure.
Figures you'd feel that way.
Uh, you trying to make A point here?
Oh, no no,
No-no-no.
Uh-oh, you uh,
Got a little sarcasm On your mouth there.
Let's just say i can relate To dave's frustrations.
And there it is.
You think dave's right 'cause you're just like him.
I'm just saying It might be nice if you showed
A tiny bit of appreciation For the work i do
To make icarly happen.
More appreciation?
You already named the show After yourself.
Well, if you don't like The name icarly,
Then maybe we should Change it to isam
Who's too lazy to even show up
For rehearsal most of the time.
Anything else you wanna get Off your chest?
It's not like You didn't get plenty Off your chest, too.
Well, if you meant Everything you said,
Then i don't even get Why you'd wanna be friends With me.
And back atcha.
Okay then.
All friends have fights.
Yeah, but this one Was different.
It wasn't even like a fight.
I mean, we didn't yell Or anything.
We just said stuff,
And it was bad.
Come on, you and sam Have been friends forever.
I know, but people change.
Mm-hmm.
That's what happened with me And my friend eddie robinson.
He got hit by a bus. Now, he deddie robinson.
Talk about change.
Try a muffin.
He told us about His dead friend
And then gave me a muffin.
'sup guys?
Hey, dave.
Hola dah-veed.
Did you come up With a funny idea
For the ishorts competition?
I thought he and fleck Broke up.
They did.
Yep.
Which is why i'm gonna make
An awesomely hilarious video By myself.
I don't need fleck's help Or anyone's.
That's right.
Okay.
Will you guys help me?
No way, seriously?
Yeah, so i got his arm Behind his back,
And i'm bending it And bending it But it won't snap,
So finally i decide that i'm--
What are you doing here?
None of your bees-cheese.
We're having A private meeting.
Good, so are me and fleck.
How nice.
T-bo!
What?
We want a table That's as far away from them As possible.
Have i ever cared Where you sit?
Come on, fleck.
I can't believe She came here.
You came here.
I always come here.
She always comes here too.
You wanna get thumped?
Look, maybe it's fate That you and sam are both here.
Why don't you go Apologize to her?
I have nothing To apologize for.
Sam's the one Who should say she's sorry.
She thinks you should say You're sorry.
Yeah, right.
I'll say i'm sorry to carly Right after t-bo graduates
From medical school.
I happen to be a doctor Of smoothie-ology.
And why don't you two Keep it down over there?
Yeah, owww!
Fleck threw a muffin at me.
Hey, no throwing muffins.
Owww.
Sam?
It slipped.
Uh, you gotta cranberry On your nose.
Oof.
I'm so sorry.
I accept your apology.
It wasn't for you.
It was for that lady i muffined.
Guys, come on.
We have a web show To do tomorrow night,
So you two better work this out.
Maybe i don't wanna Work it out.
That's fine.
I can do icarly by myself.
You can't do icarly Without me.
Yes, i can,
'cause we do it at my house And you're banned from there.
I don't wanna be there.
I don't even wanna be In the same room with you.
Well, lucky you--
There's a door.
Good, why don't you use it?
I will.
No, i will.
Come on, fleck.
Let's go, dave.
Are you okay, ma'am?
Would you like--
Aahh!
Ahh.
There's nothing like a sunny day On the high seas,
Captaining a fine,
Nautical boat.
Stop, gibby!
I'm sorry.
I squeezed the nozzle too hard.
You're supposed to create A refreshing ocean spray.
That was like a whale Peed in my face.
Well, when do we
Take this thing out On the ocean for real?
When i figure out How to pay for the dock space.
Well, it's not much fun
Being a boat boy In a parking lot.
It's called "paying your dues."
Now, swab the deck
And rotate the shuttlecock Towards the starboard bow.
I don't know What that stuff means.
Then consult Your boat boy handbook.
Hey.
Hiya.
A'ho.
Look at The pronunciation key.
Ahoy.
Your boat Is in my parking space.
I'm sorry.
They dropped it off here
And i don't have anywhere else To put it yet.
How 'bout in the ocean?
That's what i keep saying.
Gibby!
That is my spot.
My dad pays extra for it.
Why don't you And your dad come hang out
With us on the boat?
It's pretty fun,
And later on my boat boy's Gonna barbecue some chicken.
I make my own sauce.
I'm not interested In your sauce,
And i don't wanna "hang out" On your stupid boat.
You're lucky i gotta go To baseball practice.
But if that boat's still here When i get back,
I'm gonna kick your butts.
Ooooh.
Big talk from a guy Who doesn't even have a boat.
Bye bye.
Drive recklessly!
Man, that guy is such a dish--
Hey!
Save it for the chicken.
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
Hello, i'm freddie.
Thank you.
Tonight on icarly,
We embark on a bold experiment In live webcasting,
Since carly and sam Will be doing the show
From different locations.
So cross your fingers And all other parts of you.
Tonight, sam is webcasting From a super-secret location.
I'm in my living room.
It was super-secret, Now it's not.
What'd she say?
Nothing.
Helping us out tonight
Are two of the funniest Video makers ever.
My buddy dave.
What-up, web-watchers?
And here's dave's More entertaining partner, Fleck!
Love me, and you get This free knife.
Ooooh.
And now it's time For another...
Tonight...
Good evening.
Are you also a vampire?
Why no, no, no, no.
I'm a hobo.
I've never tasted the blood From the neck of a hobo.
Well i'll give you A taste of my neck blood
For a bite of that grapefruit On your face.
Pardon me,
But there is no grapefruit Upon my face.
Of course there is.
Right where you nose oughtta be.
What's wrong?
Uh, sam's signal Got scrambled, here.
I got her.
No, i do not wish to take a ride On your choo choo train.
Mua-ha-ha-ha ha-ha-ha.
Um, i haven't mentioned A choo choo train...yet.
Well, i wasn't sure,
'cause i couldn't hear you For a moment there.
Uh, sorry there vampire,
But i didn't hear What you just uttered.
Ah, if only Our technical producer Wasn't such a dip-head,
Mua-ha- ha-ha ha-ha-ha.
Maybe someone oughtta let it go And stick to the script.
Perhaps i would,
If a certain hobo Had written a better script,
Moo-ha-ha.
Well, i know A certain vampire
Who's asking for a punch In the grapefruit.
Whoa.
Things are getting pretty tense Between carly and sam.
Ah, they'll be cool.
Fish stick?
My favorite part Of the fish, captain.
Oh-oh.
Looks like trouble Off the stern port bow.
Whoa, he brought His baseball team.
Yeah, the pirates.
Hey, captain stupid,
You gonna move your boat or not?
I don't have anywhere To take it yet.
Then we're coming aboard And taking over your boat.
Huh?
Right guys, let's get 'em.
What are we gonna do?
Pelt 'em with fish sticks.
Pelt, pelt, pelt, pelt, pelt.
Get off my boat.
Okay, you got us, you got us.
No, gibby.
We never surrender this boat.
They have our boat.
But i got the sauce.
Okay, sorry about The technical difficulties Tonight,
But now that things Working again, why don't we--
Hello?
Sam?
Can you hear me?
I don't think it's working.
Freddie's such an idiot.
You're still on, freddie?
Freddie?
While we resolve These technical difficulties,
Please enjoy this pretaped video Of a man biting the heads
Off bambi dolls.
Sam, can you hear me?
I can now.
This whole thing is jank.
What whole thing?
Us doing icarly From different locations.
Please get her back So i can keep yelling at her.
Trying.
Sam, sam can you hear me Or not?
Yeah, i hear you.
I was saying it's not my fault
You guys--
Freddie,
Why am i upside down?
I'm working on it.
Uh, that's not me.
That's the mexican Dessert channel.
Thank you.
Okay you know what?
This isn't gonna work.
Yeah, no chiz.
Let's just end this.
Come on,
You guys have never stopped In the middle of a show before.
I don't mean end this show.
I mean, end icarly.
Cool with me.
You guys, you can't just...
No, no-no-no-no-no.
Sam don't--
Sam?
Carly.
Hi.
Hey.
I just texted dave.
We're all set for your guys' Shoot after school.
Good.
Whoa, i thought You were gonna help me
And fleck shoot stuff After school.
You never asked me To help you and fleck.
That doesn't mean You can just back out on me.
Don't try to intimidate him.
Fleck and i gotta finish Our video in time
For the ishorts competition, Which we're gonna win.
No, dave and i are gonna win Because we thought ahead
And made a plan with freddie To shoot our video.
I have as much of a right To freddie as you.
You do not, freddie loves me.
I can't believe You two are really breaking up.
Believe it.
Don't worry.
I know this is hard for you,
But always remember, It's not your fault.
This has been coming A long time.
And just 'cause sam and i Are splitting up,
Doesn't mean i love you Any less.
And i don't hate you any more Than i always have.
Uh.
Come on, freddie,
Let's go to study hall.
Wait, you can't just Take freddie Whenever you want him.
Uh.
Okay, maybe we should Let freddie decide
Who he wants to go with.
It's not fair To make him choose between us.
He's just a boy.
Whoa, wait, wait.
What if i wanna choose?
Fine.
I'll buy you a big High speed hard drive.
You can't buy freddie's love.
Here's $20.
All right, i can't take this.
Oh, it's okay.
She doesn't mean to hurt you.
I just want things To be the way they were.
See what you did?
You're a monster.
Hey, you guys.
Hey.
You guys shooting stuff For icarly?
No, not for icarly.
You didn't tell him That you and sam--
I'll tell him later.
Dave and i are shooting A video to try and win
This competition on ishorts.
Dave?
I'm dave.
Ishorts?
Popular website.
That guy?
Morris.
I work for lewbert.
Remember, i got that cat Outta your wall?
Well, you know.
Anyway, now that i know What's going on,
What are you guys shooting?
Just cool shots of seattle At night from the 14th floor.
From his window Washing platform.
From his--
Well holdy hold up there.
From his window Washer's platform?
Yeah.
It's completely safe.
I'm gonna put the kids In harnesses,
And i'll be there with 'em The whole time.
Oh, you'll be careful?
Promise.
Okay.
Then we're gonna put together A giant slingshot
And go buy 30 watermelons.
Sh'boom!
Okay, you all wait here.
I'll take the elevator down And get the harnesses.
Thanks.
Okay, cool.
Wow.
We're so high up.
Yeah, i bet If i spit from up here
And it hit somebody In the parking lot,
It'd go right Through their skull.
That's the boyest thing I've ever heard a boy say.
Uh, excuse me?
What are you doing here?
Why are you here?
We're here 'cause freddie's helping me
And carly shoot some stuff For the video we're making.
Out on the window Washer's platform?
Yeah, i set it up With morris.
Well i asked morris too
And he said i should meet him Here tonight, now.
Why would he tell you--
'cause if you both asked him,
He probably thought You guys wanted to shoot Stuff together.
Well, we don't.
Ryan seacrest!
Ha ha.
Sam?
You're not wearing a harness.
Ah, harnesses Are for fallers.
Get back in here.
No, me and fleck Get to go first
'cause i'm out here And you're not.
Oh, yeah?
No-no-no.
Carly, get back in here.
No, me and fleck get to go.
This is not safe.
I wouldn't do that.
Guys, get back inside,
It's way too dangerous To be out there Without a harness.
You heard him, Go back inside.
You first.
Yeah, i don't think so.
I ain't going nowhere.
Gimme that back.
Aah!
What was that?
A very large bird?
Who likes peanuts?
And nougat?
Come on, we got a job to do.
Set course For payback island.
Now, let's see What our pirate friends Are up to.
What are they doing?
Having fun.
Exceeding maximum occupancy.
Hand me a melon.
And now we pull 'er back.
So gibby, what happens When you strike a match?
Well, the friction From the match head
Against the striking surface.
Fire!
What was that?
Yeah-heh
Direct hit, sir.
Eat that, pirates.
I think they're still hungry.
Then let's fruit some jerks.
It was a watermelon.
How could a watermelon--
Two more!
Yeahh!
Shall we hit them again, sir?
Indeed we shall.
I mean it, both of you,
Get back inside right now.
I'm not going back in Unless carly goes first.
Well i'm not going back in 'till dave and i shoot
What we need for our video,
No matter how messy This wind makes my hair.
Carly, it's not worth it.
And you guys are friends, You shouldn't be fighting.
Y yeah, friends Shouldn't fight.
I just said that.
Well, i thought it Before you said it.
Liar.
Don't you call me a liar,
You better watch yourself--
Man, it's really windy Out here.
Whoa, where are they going?
Oh my god sam, we're moving.
And that's my fault?
Yes, you hit The button thingy!
Oh man, why'd i hit The button thingy?
Just make it stop.
How?
Uh, hit-the hit-the hit The red one.
You guys okay?!
I think so.
But now how are we gonna--
Uh-oh.
Aah!
Carly!!
Carly, don't let go!
Why on earth would i let go?
Sh'boom.
Aah, this is insane!
Abandon ship, abandon ship!
We did it!
Sam?
Carly, don't let go.
Okay, but can you guys Give me any other advice?
Hey, what's going on Up there?
I don't know.
Huh,
It looks like Aahh-waaaooooohhh!
What?
Sh'boom.
I'm gonna fall, I'm gonna fall!
You're not gonna fall!
Yes, i am, i'm slipping!
Don't slip.
I'm not slipping by choice, Stupid gravity!
Okay, hang on,
I'm coming to get you.
Sam, be careful.
Thanks for the tip!
Okay, momma's coming,
I'm not scared.
This is fun.
Spencer.
Carly--move!
Carly, don't let go.
Yeah, we're pretty much On the same page.
Sam, what are you doing?
Just relax.
Sam?
Here, grab my hand.
I'm scared!
Me too, just grab it.
Unh!
Sam, you're not strong enough To pull her up.
Really?
Aaah!
Yeah!
She's up on the thing.
I see her up on the thing.
Who's that guy?
Fleck.
Nice to meet you.
Come on.
Okay, i'm up.
Okay, i'm gonna throw Down a rope.
Hurry. okay.
Spencer?
Aah!
Situation, situation,
Situation!
Aah!
Come on!
Sam, grab it.
Grab the rope.
Okay, i got you, i got you.
Okay.
I got you, i got you.
Okay, wait.
Sam, watch your hand.
I did.
I'm trying.
Okay, ready?
Yeah, go.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
I'm sorry, sorry.
Okay, okay. go.
Push, push.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks so much.
Just tie it around yourselves And we'll pull you up.
Okay.
Okay guys, grab on tight
And get ready.
You girls ready?
Pull!
Pull. i'm ready!
Pull.
Guys, keep pulling.
Keep pulling.
Keep going.
Just a little bit more, c'mon!
There they are.
Gimme your hand.
Freddie help me.
Okay guys, you got it?
We got it.
Got it.
Lift your leg up.
Yeah. yeah.
You guys okay?
I think so.
We're good.
That was way too close.
No chiz.
But we made it.
Yeah.
Neither one of us Cried the whole time.
Nope, we're brave.
Yeah, we are.
I got the harnesses.
What happened?
In 5, 4, 3, 2...
I'm the carly.
I'm the sam.
And this is...
You know our little friends,
Fleck...
And dave.
Well over the past week...
We helped fleck and dave Shoot a fun little video...
For the competition At ishorts.com.
So now...
Without further schkadoo...
We present...
There's a wind coming.
A wind?
A strong wind.
Stronger than this?
Oh, yes.
How do we save ourselves From the wind?
We don't.
How can we survive?
We can't.
Will we have time To make this movie?
We won't.
No one can save you.
What's happening?!
Aah!
Where's my ointment?
I don't know!
Not even your pasta is safe.
Aah!
Tell me the name.
You don't wanna know.
Tell me the name Of this wind.
They call it...
This wind blows!
Repair and Synchronization by
Easy Subtitles Synchronizer 1.0.0.0